Only designated people may be hunted at the manor.
The Hunt is a action, thriller, horror film directed by Craig Zobel.
Twelve strangers wake up in a clearing.
They don't know where they are—or how they got there.
In the shadow of a dark internet conspiracy theory, ruthless elitists
gather at a remote location to hunt humans for sport.
But their master plan is about to be derailed when one of
the hunted turns the tables on her pursuers.
Crystal, played by Betty Gilpin.
Athena, played by Hilary Swank.
Gary, played by Ethan Suplee.
Liberty, played by Teri Wyble.
Staten Island, played by Ike Barinholtz.
Don, played by Wayne Duvall.
The Hunt is a 2020 American satirical action horror film directed by
Craig Zobel and written by Nick Cuse and Damon Lindelof.
The film stars Betty Gilpin, Hilary Swank, Ike Barinholtz, and Emma Roberts.
Jason Blum was a producer under his Blumhouse
Productions banner, along with Lindelof.
Zobel and Lindelof have said that the film is intended as a satire on the
profound political divide between the American left and right.
It is about a group of elites who kidnap working-class people to hunt them.
The film was first announced in March 2018, and the cast signed on a year later.
Filming took place in New Orleans.
The film was originally scheduled for release on September 27, 2019.
However, as a result of the El Paso and Dayton mass shootings in early
August 2019, Universal Pictures decided to delay it.
The Hunt was released in theaters in the United States on March 13, 2020, by
Universal Pictures and received mixed reviews from critics.
The onset of the COVID-19 pandemic resulted in the closure of most theaters within a week of the film's
release, which resulted in the film underperforming at the box office, grossing only $12.4 million.
Universal made The Hunt available digitally on March 20.
The film explores themes of dark comedy, gore, satire, murder, death game.
The tone is dark and intense.